---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://critterism-be.herokuapp.com/api/v1/trivia
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.6.0
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - Cowboy
      Date:
      - Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:07:56 GMT
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Type:
      - application/json; charset=utf-8
      Etag:
      - W/"d7fc50e9f95a5e4b717425ec1154db6d"
      Cache-Control:
      - max-age=0, private, must-revalidate
      X-Request-Id:
      - ba7fe320-737d-4d5e-b94e-6498dd7fa44d
      X-Runtime:
      - '0.030911'
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Via:
      - 1.1 vegur
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"data":[{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        was the name of the Ethiopian Wolf before they knew it was related to wolves?","correct_answer":"Simien
        Jackel","incorrect_answers":["Ethiopian Coyote","Amharic Fox","Canis Simiensis"],"answers":["Ethiopian
        Coyote","Amharic Fox","Canis Simiensis","Simien Jackel"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"A
        carnivorous animal eats flesh, what does a nucivorous animal eat?","correct_answer":"Nuts","incorrect_answers":["Nothing","Fruit","Seaweed"],"answers":["Nothing","Fruit","Seaweed","Nuts"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A
        slug\u0026rsquo;s blood is green.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"],"answers":["False","True"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the Gray Wolf\u0026#039;s scientific name?","correct_answer":"Canis Lupus","incorrect_answers":["Canis
        Aureus","Canis Latrans","Canis Lupus Lycaon"],"answers":["Canis Aureus","Canis
        Latrans","Canis Lupus Lycaon","Canis Lupus"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        type of creature is a Bonobo?","correct_answer":"Ape","incorrect_answers":["Lion","Parrot","Wildcat"],"answers":["Lion","Parrot","Wildcat","Ape"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the name of the copper-rich protein that creates the blue blood in the
        Antarctic octopus?","correct_answer":"Hemocyanin","incorrect_answers":["Cytochrome","Iron","Methionine"],"answers":["Cytochrome","Iron","Methionine","Hemocyanin"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"By
        definition, where does an abyssopelagic animal live?","correct_answer":"At
        the bottom of the ocean","incorrect_answers":["In the desert","On top of a
        mountain","Inside a tree"],"answers":["In the desert","On top of a mountain","Inside
        a tree","At the bottom of the ocean"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Rabbits
        can see what\u0026#039;s behind themselves without turning their heads.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"],"answers":["False","True"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the name for a male bee that comes from an unfertilized egg?","correct_answer":"Drone","incorrect_answers":["Soldier","Worker","Male"],"answers":["Soldier","Worker","Male","Drone"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the collective noun for vultures?","correct_answer":"Wake","incorrect_answers":["Ambush","Building","Gaze"],"answers":["Ambush","Building","Gaze","Wake"]}}]}'
  recorded_at: Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:07:57 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
